35 millimeter slides
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- 35 millimeter slides, 2.1.5.1
  - Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)], circa 1971; 14 (Box 1587)
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Painting of man and woman begging at his feet], 1
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Garden of Eden painting], 2
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Inside of the Sistine Chapel], 3
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Ceiling of Sistine Chapel], 4
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Close-up of a painting; a woman's face], 5
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Close-up of painting; man on cloud (God?)], 6
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Close-up of a painting; a woman's face], 7
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Close-up of painting; man being grasped by other people], 8
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Close-up of painting on Sistine Chapel ceiling; angry man (God?)], 9
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: "Creation of Adam," close-up of hands], 10
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: (Blurry picture)], 11
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Sistine Chapel], 12
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Large stone building], 13
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Inside of a grand building], 14
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Courtyard], 15
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Grand building with pillars], 16
  - Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)], circa 1971; 15 (Box 1587)
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Large building in Europe], 1
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Part of a courtyard], 2
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Inside of a building, painted ceiling], 3
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Inside of a building, pillars], 4
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Small sculptures of Jesus and Judas; Jesus with crown of thorns (with Pontius Pilot?)], 5
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Lowell Thomas at Roman amphitheatre], 6
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: City square], 7
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Roman temple], 8
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Inside of a domed building [pantheon]], 9
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Cherub statues on a bridge], 10
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: ["She - Wolf suckling Remus and Romulus", Founders of Rome] Odd creature/beast statue], 11
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Fountain with sculptures], 12
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Sculptures in front of parking lot], 13
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Person rowing a boat], 14
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Statue of a man riding a horse], 15
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Fountain], 16
  - Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)], circa 1971; 16 (Box 1587)
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Round, pillared building], 1
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: A track field], 2
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Fountain], 3
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Castle and a stone pyramid], 4
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Building with Italian words on it], 5
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: City view], 6
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Clock], 7
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Ancient ruins], 8
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas standing on a sidewalk], 9
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Ancient ruins], 10
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Ancient ruins], 11
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Ancient ruins], 12
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Archway], 13
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Ancient ruins], 14
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Archway], 15
  - Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)], circa 1971; 17 (Box 1587)
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Roman amphitheatre [colosseum]], 1
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Roman amphitheatre [colosseum]], 2
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Ancient ruins], 3
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Grand building with statues decorating the front], 4
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: City at night; ancient ruins], 5
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Archway], 6
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Grand building lit up at night], 7
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Domed building], 8
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Fountain], 9
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: [Trevi Fountain]Large fountain in front of building], 10
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Lit up city at night], 11
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Lit up city at night], 12
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Ancient building], 13
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Grand building lit up at night], 14
  - Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate] Note: An audio cassette recording titled Lowell Thomas Estate accompanies this slide presentation, undated; 18 (Box 1587)
    - Beginning of Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate] Note: An audio cassette recording titled Lowell Thomas Estate accompanies this slide presentation [: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas on beach chairs on sand], 1
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Bench in front of lake], 2
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Aerial view of land], 3
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Driveway leading up to house], 4
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas with little boy standing between them (Lowell Thomas, Jr.?)], 5
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Rolling hills, pine trees], 6
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Close-up of Frances Ryan Thomas], 7
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Lowell Thomas sitting with Frances Ryan Thomas], 8
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: (Two photos): Lowell Thomas and other men all in uniform, and Lowell Thomas with T.E. Lawrence in Arabia], 9
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Lowell Thomas with group of men in front of plane], 10
  - Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate] Note: An audio cassette recording titled Lowell Thomas Estate accompanies this slide presentation, undated; 19 (Box 1587)
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: A plaque in a rock (illegible)], 1
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Lake view], 2
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: A house hidden behind trees], 3
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Golf course], 4
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Trees by side of house], 5
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: [Illustrated] Winding path leading to large building], 6
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Article titled "The New Yorker. The Talk of the Town"], 7
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Inside of a church], 8
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Sun setting over a field], 9
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Field [Golf Course] during autumn], 10
  - Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate] Note: An audio cassette recording titled Lowell Thomas Estate accompanies this slide presentation, undated; 20 (Box 1587)
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Lake], 1
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Lake], 2
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Sunset], 3
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: A white house], 4
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: (Two photos): Close-up of a man [Richard Nixon], and Lowell Thomas talking with another man], 5
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thoams, Jr. with another man], 6
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: (Two photos): Close-up of a man, and another close-up of a different man], 7
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: (Two photos): Lowell Thomas and another man, both in flight gear, and Lowell Thoams talking with two other men], 8
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Lowell Thomas talking with Franklin Delano Roosevelt], 9
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Lowell Thomas sitting with a group of men], 10
  Box 1588
- 35 millimeter slides, 2.1.5.1
  - Carousel number 24 (continued from previous box) [Lowell Thomas Estate] Note: An audio cassette recording titled Lowell Thomas Estate accompanies this slide presentation, undated; 1 (Box 1588)
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Lowell Thomas talking with Franklin Delanor Roosevelt], 1
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Man and woman together], 2
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Sun setting over lake], 3
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Estate], 4
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Brick house], 5
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: A bedroom], 6
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Close-up of wall inside bedroom], 7
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Map of "(?) Hill Country Club"], 8
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Group of men holding golf clubs, Lowell Thomas in the center], 9
  - Carousel number 24 (continued from previous box) [Lowell Thomas Estate] Note: An audio cassette recording titled Lowell Thomas Estate accompanies this slide presentation, undated; 2 (Box 1588)
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Map of golf course], 1
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Golf course], 2
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Golf course], 3
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Photo of man swinging a golf club and a letter from Richard Nixon to Lowell Thomas about the golf club], 4
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Golf course], 5
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Estate during the winter], 6
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Flowers in backyard of house], 7
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Lake], 8
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: A sunset], 9
  - Carousel number 24 (continued from previous box) [Lowell Thomas Estate] Note: An audio cassette recording titled Lowell Thomas Estate accompanies this slide presentation, undated; 3 (Box 1588)
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: (Three photos): Flower garden, close-up of a flower, and Frances Ryan Thomas in flower garden], 1
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thoams, Jr. holding a map], 2
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: A house], 3
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Lowell Thomas holding golf clubs inside of house], 4
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Dining room], 5
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Lake on golf course], 6
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Looking up at city buildings], 7
    - [Carousel number 24 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Side view of house], 8
  - Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate], undated; 4 (Box 1588)
    - Beginning of Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate] [: Lowell Thomas with his dog], 1
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Side view of house], 2
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Lake in front of house], 3
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Lake on golf course; Captioned: Hammersley Hill], 4
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Lowell Thomas tanding with a man in uniform], 5
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Man under a tree, view of a city [Lowell Thomas reading Mount of Olives (?)]], 6
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: (Two photos): Lowell Thomas talking to a man in uniform at the Afganistan border, and Lowell Thomas on a boat being rowed by people], 7
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Lowell Thomas holding the hand of a little boy (Lowell Thomas, Jr.?)], 8
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Lowell Thomas and little boy staning on fallen tree over a lake], 9
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Lake], 10
  - Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate], undated; 5 (Box 1588)
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: People mounted on horses], 1
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: A barn [House (?)]], 2
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Lake], 3
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Golf course], 4
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: People on gofl course], 5
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Portrait of a man], 6
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Painting of ships on water and submarines], 7
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: A chapel], 8
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: A chapel], 9
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Lake], 10
  - Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate], undated; 6 (Box 1588)
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: A forest], 1
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Lake], 2
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Path lined with trees], 3
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Lowell Thomas with a horse], 4
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Franklin Delano Roosevelt], 5
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Lowell Thomas standing with a man on steps], 6
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: (Two photos): Close-up of a man, and group of people in Arabic garb], 7
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: (Two photos): Lowell Thomas laughing with two other men, and Lowell Thomas with four other men], 8
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Lowell Thomas with a group of men], 9
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Person standing up in car, waving his hat and another man standing next to him], 10
  - Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate], undated; 7 (Box 1588)
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Group of men, Lowell Thomas in the back row], 1
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: People performing a dance], 2
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Lowell Thomas in a row boat, reading a newspaper], 3
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Man mounted on a horse], 4
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: A brick house], 5
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: A living room], 6
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: A brick house], 7
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Machinery], 8
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Lowell Thomas standing with a group of men], 9
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Golf course], 10
  - Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate], undated; 8 (Box 1588)
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Lowell Thoams standing with three other men], 1
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Golf course], 2
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Golf course], 3
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Lowell Thomas in a golf cart with another man], 4
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Golf course], 5
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Road and cherry trees], 6
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Golf course], 7
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Close-up of flowers], 8
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: House], 9
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Back of house], 10
  - Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate] [Items 1-7] Carousel number 26 [Items 8-12], undated; 9 (Box 1588)
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Lowell Thomas giving a broadcast in front of world map painted on wall], 1
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Indoor pool], 2
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: curved staircase], 3
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: A bedroom], 4
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: (Four photos): Lowell Thomas with a group of men, Lowell Thomas standing with another man on steps, Lowell Thomas talking to Franklin Delano Roosevelt, and Group of men, Lowell Thomas standing in the back row], 5
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Lowell Thomas by his red golf cart], 6
    - [Carousel number 25 [Lowell Thomas Estate]: Lake by golf course], 7
    - [Carousel number 26: On a boat, sun setting on ocean horizon], 8
    - [Carousel number 26: Ship sailing on icy water], 9
    - [Carousel number 26: Ship sailing on icy water], 10
    - [Carousel number 26: Wave hitting a ship], 11
    - [Carousel number 26: Ship stuck in ice], 12
  - Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin] Note: An audio cassette recording and a transcript titled Schooner Bowdoin accompany this slide presentation, undated; 10 (Box 1588)
    - Beginning of Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin] Note: An audio cassette recording and a transcript titled Schooner Bowdoin accompany this slide presentation: [Ship turning over on its side], 1
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Boat on water and a row boat], 2
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Sailboat, Captioned: "The Schooner Bowdoin Sails Again"], 3
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Sailboat], 4
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Sailboat], 5
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Men on sailboat], 6
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Boat at dock], 7
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Ship docked], 8
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Large boat on water, ship beside it], 9
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: View from on a boat, mountains ahead], 10
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Iceberg], 11
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Man at wheel of boat], 12
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Person standing on top of icy mound], 13
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Boat stuck in ice], 14
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Boat on icy water], 15
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Sailboat], 16
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Lifeboat], 17
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Boat masts], 18
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Man tying rope to pole], 19
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Man looking up at top of boat], 20
  - Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin] Note: An audio cassette recording and a transcript titled Schooner Bowdoin accompany this slide presentation, undated; 11 (Box 1588)
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Lifeboat with life jackets], 1
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Wave crashing onto boat], 2
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Body of water, mountains], 3
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Boat], 4
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Ice], 5
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Ice], 6
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Ship on sea], 7
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Ship on sea], 8
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Snowy mountains], 9
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Boat that says "Bowdoin, Boston"], 10
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Men working on ship], 11
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Boats on water, people on dock watching], 12
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Crowd of people on boat], 13
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: "Bowdoin"], 14
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Man smoking a pipe on boat], 15
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Boat on icy water], 16
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Man on boat], 17
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Man at wheel on boat], 18
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Man at wheel on boat], 19
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Two men on boat, conversing], 20
  - Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin] Note: An audio cassette recording and a transcript titled Schooner Bowdoin accompany this slide presentation, undated; 12 (Box 1588)
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Deck of boat], 1
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Deck of boat], 2
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Boat leaning to right], 3
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Man on boat], 4
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Man looking at icy water from boat], 5
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Sailboat], 6
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Sinking ship], 7
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Map showing the North Pole], 8
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Boat on icy water], 9
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Boat on icy water], 10
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Boat on water], 11
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Man climbing to top of boat], 12
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: People on boat looking at mountains], 13
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Men on deck of boat], 14
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Woman with man at wheel of boat], 15
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Campus of Bowdoin College], 16
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Man holding American flag], 17
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Man wearing a fur coat], 18
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Deck of boat], 19
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Boat on icy water], 20
  - Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin] Note: An audio cassette recording and a transcript titled Schooner Bowdoin accompany this slide presentation, undated; 13 (Box 1588)
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Boat on icy water], 1